themodernman.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy - The Modern Man

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, process, and disclose your information, including personal information, in conjunction with your access to and use of TheModernMan.com’s website. We may change or add to this Privacy Policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically.

When this Privacy Policy mentions "TheModernMan.com”, “we”, “us” or “our”, it refers to Capital Web Group Limited (“TheModernMan.com”), which is the company that is responsible for your information under this Privacy Policy (“Data Controller”).

Information collected on our website is stored on our web servers in Canada. Our registered company is located in Hong Kong. By using the TheModernMan.com, you consent to the transfer of your data overseas and across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. The laws governing data in your home country may differ from those in the countries to which data is transferred. By accessing and using our website, you consent to the transfer of your data in this manner.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We ask for and collect the following personal information about you when you use TheModernMan.com’s website, which is necessary for the performance of a contract between you and us (e.g. placing an order) and to allows us to comply with various legal obligations. Without this information, we may not be able to provide you with all of the requested services.

**Account Information**  
When you create a TheModernMan.com account via our website, we require information such as your first and last name and email address.

**Order Information**  
When you place an order on our website, we request that you provide additional information such as your billing address. Your billing address is required to validate your payment information only. We will never send any item to your billing address.

**Payment Information**  
To facilitate processing of payments on our website, we require you to provide certain financial information (e.g. your credit card number).

**Communications with TheModernMan.com**  
When you communicate with TheModernMan.com via our website (e.g. for customer service inquiries), we collect information about your communication and any information you choose to provide.

When you use TheModernMan.com, we automatically collect information, including personal information, about the services you use and how you use them, such as information about how you use or interact with our website, view or interact with our content, and information about your computer or mobile device. This information may include:

**Usage Information**  
We collect information about your interactions with our website such as the pages or content you view and other actions on TheModernMan.com’s website.

**Device Information**  
We automatically collect device information when you access our website, even if you have not created a TheModernMan.com account or logged in. That information includes, among other things: your IP address, operating system version, device type, system and performance information, and browser type.

**Log Data**  
Like most websites today, our web servers keep log files that record data each time a device accesses those servers. The log files contain data about the nature of each access, including IP addresses, internet service providers, files viewed on our website, operating system versions, device type, and timestamps.

**Local Storage**  
TheModernMan.com may collect and store information – including personal information – locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage.

**Cookies and Similar Technologies**  
TheModernMan.com may set and access cookies on your computer. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). We may also set and access device identifiers which may include your IP address, user agent information (e.g. browser version, OS type, and version), and device-provided identifiers. 

TheModernMan.com uses 3rd party vendor remarketing technologies that use tracking cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie, Google Analytics tracking cookie and Facebook tracking cookie. This means we may show ads to you across the internet, specifically on the Google Search Network, Google Display Network, YouTube and on Facebook. As always, we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s, Facebook's or any other 3rd party remarketing system.

The third-party vendors, including Google and Facebook, whose services we use will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our products and services to those who have shown interest in our products and services.

You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager at <https://adssettings.google.com/u/0/authenticated>. Also, you can opt out of other third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit [http://networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/)

**Payment Transaction Information**  
TheModernMan.com, or its third-party agents, collects information related to your payment transactions through our website, including the payment instrument used, date and time, payment amount, payment instrument expiration date, billing post code, PayPal email address (if PayPal payment method is used), your address and other related transaction details. This information is necessary for the adequate performance of the contract between you and TheModernMan.com for provision of payment services.

#### HOW WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

TheModernMan.com (or our third-party agents) uses, stores, and processes information, including personal information, about you to provide, understand, improve, and develop TheModernMan.com’s website and comply with our various legal obligations. Examples of this are:

  * Enabling you to access and use TheModernMan.com’s website.
  * Operating, protecting, improving, and optimizing TheModernMan.com’s website and experience, such as by performing analytics and conducting research.
  * Enabling you to access and use our payment services (e.g. Credit / Debit Cards, PayPal, etc.) to place orders.
  * Sending you service or support messages.

Providing you a custom user-experience through things such as:

  * Sending promotional messages, marketing, advertising, and other information that may be of interest to you, unless you indicate a preference to opt-out of receiving these communications (you can opt out of marketing communications at any time by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in such emails).
  * Showing you custom remarketing advertising on the Google Adwords and Google Display networks, YouTube and Facebook based on the pages you have visited on our site and the interest you have shown in our products.
  * Personalizing, measuring, and improving advertising to be more tailored to your interests in products, content type, etc..

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information and providing you with order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you.
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud.
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

#### HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We work with various third-party partners who help us provide and improve our products and services. We don’t sell any of your information to anyone. We have summarized how we share the information we collect below.

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

TheModernMan.com may disclose your information, including personal information, to courts, law enforcement, or governmental authorities, or authorized third parties, if and to the extent we are required or permitted to do so by law or if such disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

  * Comply with our legal obligations.
  * Comply with legal process and to respond to claims or demands asserted against TheModernMan.com.
  * Respond to verified requests relating to a criminal investigation or alleged or suspected illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other of our users to legal liability.
  * To enforce and administer our Terms and Conditions or other agreements.
  * Protect the rights, property, or personal safety of TheModernMan.com, its employees, or members of the public.

TheModernMan.com uses a variety of third-party service providers to help us provide services related to the TheModernMan.com website and our services. Service providers may be located inside or outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”). For example, services providers may help us:

  * Conduct fraud prevention and risk assessments.
  * Perform product development, maintenance, and debugging.
  * Provide customer service, advertising, payment, and transactional services.
  * Help us track website analytics, such as conversion and traffic metrics.
  * Verify information against public databases.

TheModernMan.com may need to share your information, including personal information, in order to ensure the adequate performance of our contract with you (e.g. name and billing address to complete a transaction).

#### BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING

We use your behavioural information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work>.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by Facebook and Google at:

  * Facebook <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>
  * Google <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

#### SECURITY

We have processes in place to ensure the security of your personal information, including encryption of all data when it is transferred to our service providers and limitations on access to personal information within our organisation. We use the highest level of security (up to 256 bit encryption - the level of encryption that banks use) to offer totally safe and secure transactions. So, you can rest assured that communications between your browser and TheModernMan.com's web servers are private and secure.

#### ACCOUNT DATA RETENTION

If you hold an account with TheMdoernMan.com, we do not delete the data in your account unless we receive a request from you to do so. You are responsible for the control and time periods for which you retain this data.

#### SAFETY OF MINORS

Use of TheModernMan.com website is not intended for and may not be used by individuals under the age of 13 located in the United States or under the age of 16 if located outside of the United States (or under a lower age if permitted by the laws of their residence). TheModernMan.com does not knowingly collect personal data from minors or allow them to register accounts. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a minor, we may delete this information without notice. If you have reason to believe this has occurred, please email [privacy@themodernman.com](mailto:privacy@themodernman.com)

#### YOUR RIGHTS

TheModernMan.com acknowledges your right to access your personal data. Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we must keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.

We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (e.g. developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup systems).

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.

You have the right to request information about the personal data we hold on you. If your data is incorrect, incomplete, or irrelevant you can ask to have the information corrected or removed. To access or update your personal information, email [privacy@themodernman.com](mailto:privacy@themodernman.com) with your current contact information and the personal information you would like to access. We will provide you the personal information requested if reasonably available, or will describe the types of personal information we typically collect.

**Customers Located in the EEA**  
Notwithstanding the above, customers located in the EEA may exercise any of the rights described in this section by sending an email to [privacy@themodernman.com](mailto:privacy@themodernman.com). Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before taking further action on your request.

**Managing Your Information**  
You may access and update some of your information, including personal information, through your TheModernMan.com account. You are responsible for keeping your personal information up-to-date.

**Rectification Of Inaccurate Or Incomplete Information**  
You have the right to ask us to correct inaccurate or incomplete personal information concerning you (and which you cannot update yourself within your TheModernMan.com account).

**Data Access And Portability**  
In some jurisdictions, applicable law may entitle you to request copies of your personal information held by us.

**Data Retention And Erasure**  
We generally retain your personal information for as long as is necessary for the performance of the contract between you and us and to comply with our legal obligations. If you no longer want us to use your information to provide the TheModernMan.com website to you, you can request that we erase your personal information and close your TheModernMan.com account. Please note that if you request the erasure of your personal information:

  * We may retain some of your personal information as necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as fraud detection and prevention and enhancing safety.
  * We may retain and use your personal information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations. For example, TheModernMan.com may keep some of your information for tax, legal and auditing obligations.
  * Because we maintain the TheModernMan.com website to protect from accidental or malicious loss and destruction, residual copies of your personal information may not be removed from our backup systems for a limited period of time.

**Withdrawing Consent And Restriction Of Processing**  
Where you have provided your consent to the processing of your personal information by TheModernMan.com, you may withdraw your consent at any time by changing your account settings, or by sending a communication to TheModernMan.com specifying which consent you are withdrawing. Please note that the withdrawal of your consent does not affect the lawfulness of any processing activities based on such consent before its withdrawal. Additionally, in some jurisdictions, applicable law may give you the right to limit the ways in which we use your personal information, in particular, where:

  * You contest the accuracy of your personal information.
  * The processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your personal information.
  * We no longer need your personal information for the purposes of the processing, but you require the information for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.

**Objection To Processing**  
In some jurisdictions, applicable law may entitle you to require TheModernMan.com not to process your personal information for certain specific purposes where such processing is based on legitimate interest. If you object to such processing, TheModernMan.com will no longer process your personal information for these purposes unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for such processing or such processing is required for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claim(s).

Where your personal information is processed for direct marketing purposes, you may, at any time, ask TheModernMan.com to cease processing your data for these direct marketing purposes by emailing [privacy@themodernman.com](mailto:privacy@themodernman.com).

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

TheModernMan.com reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. If you disagree with the revised Privacy Policy, you may cancel your TheModernMan.com account.

#### CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or TheModernMan.com's information handling practices, you may contact us by emailing [privacy@themodernman.com](mailto:privacy@themodernman.com)
